# **Jack Youkstetter**

## Full Stack Developer

Web developer and jack of all trades; 5+ years of javascript programming experience with a variety of skills ranging from 3D/animated frontend design to working with cloud interfaces and building api/database infrastructure. Currently pursuing a bachelors in CS.

## PORTFOLIO: https://splash-portfolio-mu.vercel.app/

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Lead Developer**

Oct 2022 - Present

Vortex Consulting - Remote

- Led the design, development, and deployment of Vive Consulting's agent booking platform, Vortex.
- Built with React + GraphQL + MongoDB and deployment with Heroku by Salesforce.

## **IT Logistics Team Lead**

Dec 2021 - Present

Northbay Networks - Emeryville, CA

- Redesigned company website for upcoming rebrand. Currently under approval by management. <a href="https://remota-website.vercel.app">https://remota-website.vercel.app</a>
- Led fulfillment team in the IT asset management department of Northbay Networks.
- Software reimaging + hardware refurbishment

#### FREELANCE PROJECTS

## **Frontend Developer**

Jan 30 2023 - Febuary 17 2022

2023 DeveloperWeek Hackathon - Azure/Oracle/Zoom Challenges

- Winner of the overall 1st place prize, 1st place in the Zoom SDK challenge, and 2nd place for the Oracle Cloud micro services challenge
- (React/OCI (Oracle Cloud Infrastructure)) Working with a team of 5 to engineer a kiosk IoT device (including a machine learning FAQ generator) for use at public transport facilities.

## **Lead Developer**

Sept 2022 - Oct 2022

Lets' Frickin Game

 (MERN + apollo graphQL) Led team of 4 in building a 'looking for group' platform dedicated to finding teams for multi-player video games

## **Full Stack Developer**

July 2022 - Aug 2022

Offload

 (ExpressJS + SQL + handlebars) Worked with team of 4 in developing a marketplace app for free goods & garage sales

#### CONTACT

- · Oakland, CA (Open to Remote)
- · +1 (510) 508-0618
- iackvoukstetter1@gmail.com
- · LinkedIn: Jack Youkstetter
- · Github: JackYouk

### **SKILLS**

#### Languages:

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Python
- Git

### Front End:

- webGL (three.js + R3F)
- React
- Next
- Redux
- · Css + scss + tailwind

#### Back End:

- Node
- Cloud platforms (AWS/Google/Oracle)
- GraphQL (apollo)
- NoSQL/mongoDB/firebase
- · SQL
- Express

## Soft Skills:

- · Team Leadership
- Creative Direction + Design
- · Consulting & sales

#### Other:

- Writing Documentation
- Docker
- QA + Jest
- · UIX Design + Figma
- Scrummastery

## **EDUCATION**

**UC Berkeley Extension**Full Stack Bootcamp

Laney College